DEAN COMPTON

SOFTWARE ENGINEER





deancompton194@yahoo.com

dcompt4.github.io

Gonzales, LA 70737

PROFILE

I am ready to utilize my technical knowledge and skills to contribute to the growth of the organization while gaining professional experience. I have worked on many interdisciplinary teams which has strengthened my communication skills and technical abilities.

SKILLS

- Experience in CSS, HTML, Java,
 JavaScript, PHP, SQL
- Design Thinking
- · Problem-Solving
- Interface design and implementation
- Project Management
- Databases

EXPERIENCE

INTERN/SOFTWARE ENGINEER

TAG Data Solutions, LLC

01/2022 - Present

- Works individually and on a team to develop dynamic web applications
- Understand clients' needs and translate them to design and development

STUDENT WORKER (WEB DEVELOPER)

Aquatic Germplasm and Genetic Resources Center | Baton Rouge

08/2019 - 01/2022

- Worked on an interdisciplinary team to design and build the AGGRC website
- Focused on front-end development while learning aspects of back-end

INDUSTRY BASED CERTIFICATION

Operation Spark

12/2018

- Industry Based Certification (IBC) in Fundamentals of JavaScript,
 Functional Programming and Web Development
- Completed coursework in an after-school program focused on introducing high school students to the fundamentals of HTML, CSS, and JavaScript.

EDUCATION

SECONDARY SCHOOL

St. Amant High School | St. Amant, LA GPA: 4.6875

2015 - 2019

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE

Major: Software Engineering Minor: Digital Media Arts and

Engineering

Louisiana State University And A&M

College | Baton Rouge, LA

GPA: 4.01 2019 - 2023